Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Anson Phelps Stokes correspondence and subject files, 1899-1929; Series II
  - Education and Special Training, 1918 (Box 42, Folder 535)
  - Educational Plans for American Expeditionary Forces, 1918 (Box 42, Folder 536)
  - Educational Policy, Committee on: minutes, 1920-1921 (Box 42, Folder 537)
  - Educational Policy Reports, 1914-1919 (Box 42, Folder 538)
  - Educational Policy Reports, 1918-1919 (Box 42, Folder 539)
  - Educational Policy Reports, 1919 March (Box 42, Folder 539a)
  - Edwards, F. Boyd, 1914-1917 (Box 42, Folder 540)
  - Ef-Ei, 1903-1928 (Box 42, Folder 541)
  - El, 1902-1929 (Box 42, Folder 542-544)
  - Elder, Samuel J., 1905-1917 (Box 42, Folder 545)
  - Ellicott, Charles R., 1910-1919 (Box 43, Folder 546)
  - Elliot Corporation, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 547)
  - Em-En, 1902-1929 (Box 43, Folder 548-549)
  - Embree, Edwin Rogers, 1909-1923 (Box 43, Folder 550-556)
  - Embree, Edwin Rogers: weekly reports on the clipping service, 1911-1913 (Box 43, Folder 557)
  - Embree, Edwin Rogers: weekly reports on the clipping service, 1914-1915 (Box 44, Folder 558)
  - Embree, Edwin Rogers: correspondence regarding his successor, 1917 (Box 44, Folder 559)
  - Emery, Henry C., 1902-1918 (Box 44, Folder 560)
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1928 (Box 44, Folder 561)
  - Endowment Campaign, 1925-1928 (Box 44, Folder 562-566)
  - Endowment Fund Booklet, 1926-1927 (Box 44, Folder 567)
  - Endowment Fund Dinners, 1927 (Box 44, Folder 568)
  - Engineering, 1915-1920 (Box 44, Folder 569)
  - English, Harry C., 1911-1912 (Box 44, Folder 570)
  - Eno Foundation Prizes, 1923-1925 (Box 44, Folder 571)
  - Ep-Es, 1903-1916 (Box 44, Folder 572)
  - Ep-Es, 1917-1928 (Box 45, Folder 573)
  - Ev, 1905-1928 (Box 45, Folder 574-575)
  - Evans, Alexander W., 1911-1927 (Box 45, Folder 576)
  - Evarts, Allen W., 1902-1914 (Box 45, Folder 577)
  - Evarts, Allen W., 1915 (Box 45, Folder 578)
  - Evarts, Allen W., 1916-1923 (Box 45, Folder 579)
  - Evarts, Harold C., 1911-1913 (Box 45, Folder 580)
  - Ew-Ez, 1905-1926 (Box 45, Folder 581)
  - Exemption papers, 1918-1919 (Box 45, Folder 582)
  - Expenses, 1915-1922 (Box 45, Folder 583)
  - Fa-Fan, 1903-1926 (Box 45, Folder 584)
  - Fackenthal, Frank D., 1911-1923 (Box 45, Folder 585)
  - Faculty, 1917-1927 (Box 45, Folder 586)
  - Faculty Club, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 587)
  - Faculty Editorial Applications, 1922 (Box 45, Folder 588)
  - Fairchild, Fred R., 1908-1926 (Box 45, Folder 589)
  - Fairchild, Henry P., 1914-1919 (Box 46, Folder 590)
  - Far, 1902-1929 (Box 46, Folder 591)
  - Farnum, Henry W., 1901-1924 (Box 46, Folder 592-594)
  - Farnum, Thomas W., 1909-1920 May (Box 46, Folder 595-596)
  - Farnum, William W., 1903-1921 (Box 46, Folder 597)
  - Farr, Hollon A., 1908-1919 (Box 46, Folder 598)
  - Farrand, Max, 1908-1926 (Box 46, Folder 599-601)
  - Farrand, Beatrix Mrs. Max [Cadwalader (Jones)], 1917-1919 (Box 47, Folder 602)
  - Farrington, Frederic E., 1914-1915 (Box 47, Folder 603)
  - Farwell, John V., 1901-1929 (Box 47, Folder 604-606)
  - Fas-Fay, 1901-1928 (Box 47, Folder 607)
  - Faunce, W.H.P., 1901-1921 (Box 47, Folder 608)
  - Fe, 1901-1928 (Box 47, Folder 609-410)
  - Feakins, William B., 1910-1911 (Box 47, Folder 611)
  - Ferry, Charles A., 1927 (Box 47, Folder 612)
  - Ferry, Charles A.: Memorial, 1926 (Box 47, Folder 613)
  - Feuillerat, Albert, 1919-1922 (Box 47, Folder 614)
  - Fi-Fir, 1901-1928 (Box 47, Folder 615)
  - Fields, Curtis P., 1899-1917 (Box 48, Folder 616)
  - Figlia d"Italia Prizes, 1924 (Box 48, Folder 617)
  - Finance, Committee on, 1920 (Box 48, Folder 618)
  - Fis, 1901-1927 (Box 48, Folder 619)
  - Fisher, George P., 1900-1914 (Box 48, Folder 620)
  - Fisher, H.J., 1901-1921 (Box 48, Folder 621)
  - Fisher, Irving, 1903-1929 (Box 48, Folder 622)
  - Fisher, Samuel H., 1901-1919 March (Box 48, Folder 623-628)
  - Fisher, Samuel H., 1919 April-1929 (Box 49, Folder 629-633)
  - Fisher, Vierva P.(Mrs. J. Ellis), 1918 (Box 49, Folder 634)
  - Fit, 1905-1928 (Box 49, Folder 635)
  - Fitch, Albert Parker, 1910-1917 (Box 49, Folder 636)
  - Fitkin Memorial: with architectural drawing, 1928-1929 (Box 49, Folder 637)
  - Fitzgerald, David E., 1917-1921 (Box 49, Folder 638)
  - Fl, 1901-1926 (Box 49, Folder 639-640)
  - Flag, 1923 (Box 49, Folder 641)
  - Flanders, James G., 1903-1914 (Box 49, Folder 642)
  - Flanders, Roger Y., 1910-1914 (Box 50, Folder 643)
  - Flexner, Abraham, 1910-1926 (Box 50, Folder 644-646)
  - Flint, Joseph Marshall, 1907-1921 (Box 50, Folder 647-648)
  - Foa-Foo, 1904-1926 (Box 50, Folder 649-650)
  - Foch, Marshall: Convocation, 1921 (Box 50, Folder 651)
  - Football films, 1923 (Box 50, Folder 652)
  - Football films: Yale-Harvard-Princeton, 1923 (Box 50, Folder 653)
  - Football ticket distribution, 1928, undated (Box 50, Folder 654)
  - For, 1901-1928 (Box 50, Folder 655)
  - Form Letters, 1910-1911 (Box 50, Folder 656)
  - Forrest, Richard E., 1913-1914 (Box 50, Folder 657)
  - Fos-Foy, 1901-1926 (Box 51, Folder 658-659)
  - Fosdick, Harry Emerson, 1909-1920 (Box 51, Folder 660)
  - Foster, Charles R., 1912 (Box 51, Folder 661)
  - Fowler, George S., 1907-1927 (Box 51, Folder 662)
  - Fra, 1903-1926 (Box 51, Folder 663-644)
  - Franklin, Benjamin, 1922 (Box 51, Folder 665)
  - Fre, 1902-1928 (Box 51, Folder 666-667)
  - Fri, 1907-1927 (Box 51, Folder 668)
  - Fro-Fry, 1905-1929 (Box 51, Folder 669)
  - Fu-Fy, 1903-1929 (Box 51, Folder 670)
  - Fuller, Philo C., 1911-1919 (Box 52, Folder 671)
  - Furst, Clyde, 1911-1925 (Box 52, Folder 672)
  - Ga-Gai, 1901-1929 (Box 52, Folder 673)
  - Gage, Brownell, 1903-1918 (Box 52, Folder 674)
  - Gal-Gan, 1901-1927 (Box 52, Folder 675-676)
  - Gar, 1903-1917 (Box 52, Folder 677-678)
  - Far, 1918-1929 (Box 52, Folder 679)
  - Gat-Gay, 1905-1929 (Box 52, Folder 680-681)
  - Ge, 1904-1922 (Box 52, Folder 682-683)
  - Ge, 1923-1929 (Box 53, Folder 684)
  - Gesell, Arnold, 1911-1920 (Box 53, Folder 685)
  - Gi, 1901-1929 (Box 53, Folder 686-688)
  - Gilling, Francis T., 1900-1918 (Box 53, Folder 689)
  - Gl, 1903-1928 (Box 53, Folder 690)
  - Glee Club, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 691)
  - Go-Gok, 1905-1928 (Box 53, Folder 692)
  - Godard, Porter B., 1902-1927 (Box 53, Folder 693)
  - Gol-Gom, 1903-1929 (Box 53, Folder 694)
  - Goo, 1901-1915 (Box 53, Folder 695)
  - Goo, 1916-1928 (Box 54, Folder 696)
  - Gooch, F. A., 1901-1918 (Box 54, Folder 697)
  - Goodell, Thomas D., 1905-1925 (Box 54, Folder 698)
  - Goodell, J. Harriett (Mrs. T.D.) (Box 54, Folder 698)
  - Gor, 1903-1929 (Box 54, Folder 699-700)
  - Goo-Goy, 1903-1925 (Box 54, Folder 701)
  - Gra-Grah, 1907-1928 (Box 54, Folder 702)
  - Graduate School, 1907-1929 (Box 54, Folder 703)
  - Gran, 1901-1922 (Box 54, Folder 704)
  - Gras-Gray, 1902-1924 (Box 54, Folder 705)
  - Graves, Henry S., 1901-1908 (Box 54, Folder 706)
  - Graves, Henry S., 1909-1929 (Box 55, Folder 707)
  - Gre, 1901-1927 (Box 55, Folder 708-509)
  - Greene, A. Crawford, 1912-1915 (Box 55, Folder 710)
  - Greene, Edward B., 1907-1929 (Box 55, Folder 711)
  - Greene, Jerome D., 1903-1921 (Box 55, Folder 712)
  - Greenway, James C., 1909-1928 (Box 55, Folder 713-714)
  - Gregory, Herbert E., 1903-1928 (Box 55, Folder 715)
  - Gri, 1903-1920 (Box 55, Folder 716-717)
  - Griffin, William V., 1908-1919 (Box 55, Folder 718)
  - Griggs, Maitland F., 1902-1926 (Box 55, Folder 718a)
  - Griswold, Charles D., 1908 (Box 55, Folder 719)
  - Griswold, William E.S., 1903-1927 (Box 56, Folder 720-721)
  - Gro, 1903-1926 (Box 56, Folder 722)
  - Group Insurance, 1929 (Box 56, Folder 723)
  - Gru, 1901-1924 (Box 56, Folder 724)
  - Greuner, Gustav, 1903-1924 (Box 56, Folder 725-726)
  - Gu, 1902-1928 (Box 56, Folder 727-728)
  - Guest Book, 1923-1924 (Box 56, Folder 729)
  - Gutenberg Bible, 1926 (Box 56, Folder 730)
  - Ha-Hak, 1906-1929 (Box 56, Folder 731-732)
  - Hackett, Edmond Byrne, 1912-1915 (Box 56, Folder 733)
  - Hadley, Arthur T., 1903-1907 (Box 56, Folder 734)
  - Hadley, Arthur T., 1908-1929 (Box 57, Folder 735-745)
  - Hadley Portrait Fund, 1921 (Box 57, Folder 746)
  - Haight, Charles C., 1902-1915 (Box 57, Folder 747)
  - Hal, 1900-1927 (Box 57, Folder 748-750)
  - Hall, Nathan, 1908-1925 (Box 58, Folder 751)
  - Hall, Porter T., 1914-1916 (Box 58, Folder 752)
  - Hall, William Edwin, 1911-1912 (Box 58, Folder 753)
  - Halsey, John R., 1914-1915 (Box 58, Folder 754)
  - Ham, 1906-1928 (Box 58, Folder 755-756)
  - Ham, George Conrad, 1912-1913 (Box 58, Folder 757)
  - Hamlin, Herbert, 1911 (Box 58, Folder 758)
  - Hammond, John Henry, 1901-1922 (Box 58, Folder 759)
  - Han-Hap, 1900-1926 (Box 58, Folder 760)
  - Hannaford, Jule M., Jr., 1922-1929 (Box 58, Folder 761)
  - Har, 1899-1927 (Box 58, Folder 762-769)
  - Harkness, Edward S., 1906-1921 (Box 59, Folder 770)
  - Harkness, William L. (Box 59, Folder 771)
  - Harkness, William L., Hall dedication, 1917-1927 (Box 59, Folder 772)
  - Harkness miscellaneous, 1905-1917 (Box 59, Folder 773)
  - Harkness Quadrangle: cornerstone ceremony, 1917 (Box 59, Folder 774)
  - Harkness-Harvard (Box 59, Folder 775)
  - Harriman, William Averil, 1913-1919 (Box 59, Folder 776)
  - Harrison, Ross G., 1907-1926 (Box 59, Folder 777-778)
  - Harvard Clubs, New England Federation of, Meetings, 1927-1928 (Box 59, Folder 779)
  - Has-Hau, 1902-1929 (Box 59, Folder 780-781)
  - Haskins and Sells, 1910-1920 (Box 59, Folder 782)
  - Haslam, Lewis S., 1905-1915 (Box 59, Folder 783)
  - Hastings, Thomas, 1907-1925 (Box 59, Folder 784)
  - Hav-Haw, 1907-1928 (Box 59, Folder 785)
  - Havana, University of: exchange professorships, 1920-1928 (Box 59, Folder 786)
  - Hawes, James Anderson, 1906-1920 (Box 59, Folder 787)
  - Hay-Haz, 1901-1929 (Box 59, Folder 788-789)
  - Hay, Louis C., 1909-1915 (Box 60, Folder 790)
  - Hay, Southard, 1905-1927 (Box 60, Folder 791)
  - Hea-Hek, 1900-1925 (Box 60, Folder 792-793)
  - Headmaster"s Association, meeting, 1924-1925 (Box 60, Folder 794)
  - Heald, John Oxenbridge, 1907-1911 (Box 60, Folder 795)
  - Hel-Hem, 1905-1929 (Box 60, Folder 796)
  - Hemmingway, Samuel B., 1913-1921 (Box 60, Folder 797)
  - Hen-Hep, 1900-1926 (Box 60, Folder 798-799)
  - Henderson, Yandell, 1905-1928 (Box 60, Folder 800)
  - Hendrickson, George L., 1907-1926 (Box 60, Folder 801)
  - Henry, Burns, 1910-1914 (Box 60, Folder 802)
  - Her-Hes, 1904-1926 (Box 60, Folder 803)
  - Hering, Henry, 1913-1915 (Box 60, Folder 804)
  - Herr, Edwin M., 1906-1928 (Box 60, Folder 805)
  - Het-Hey, 1905-1927 (Box 60, Folder 806)
  - Hi, 1901-1929 (Box 61, Folder 807-809)
  - Hibben, John Grier, 1906-1922 (Box 61, Folder 810)
  - Hidden, Edward, 1904-1919 (Box 61, Folder 811-812)
  - Hill, 1902-1925 (Box 61, Folder 813)
  - Hill, George E., 1908-1915 (Box 61, Folder 814-815)
  - Hillhouse, James, 1909-1919 (Box 61, Folder 816)
  - Hillhouse, James v. Yale University pp. 1-300, 1912 (Box 61, Folder 817)
  - Hillhouse, James v. Yale University pp. 301-629, 1912 (Box 62, Folder 818)
  - Hillhouse, James v. Yale University pp. 630-900, 1912 (Box 62, Folder 819)
  - Hillhouse, James v. Yale University pp. 901-1111, 1912 (Box 62, Folder 820)
  - Hillhouse, James v. Yale University J.K. Beaches File: pp. 1-150, 1902-1912 (Box 62, Folder 821)
  - Hillhouse, James v. Yale University J.K. Beaches File: pp. 151-295, 1902-1912 (Box 62, Folder 822)
  - Hillhouse, James v. Yale University exhibits and papers, 1912 (Box 62, Folder 823)
  - Hillhouse, James v. Yale University exhibits and papers, 1912 (Box 63, Folder 824)
  - Hillhouse, James v. Yale University exhibits and papers, 1912 (Box 63, Folder 825)
  - Hillhouse, James v. Yale University exhibits and papers, 1912 (Box 63, Folder 826)
  - Hine, Charles D., 1906-1919 (Box 63, Folder 827)
  - Hoa-Hoh, 1904-1927 (Box 63, Folder 828-829)
  - Hobson, Henry W., 1914-1918 (Box 63, Folder 830)
  - Hoffecker, James H., Jr., 1913-1915 (Box 63, Folder 831)
  - Hol, 1903-1925 (Box 63, Folder 832-833)
  - Holcomb, Marcus H., 1915-1921 (Box 63, Folder 834)
  - Holmes, Samuel Van Vranken, 1909-1913 (Box 64, Folder 835)
  - Holt, Hamilton, 1908-1920 (Box 64, Folder 836)
  - Holt, Henry, 1912-1920 (Box 64, Folder 837)
  - Hom-Hon, 1903-1919 (Box 64, Folder 838)
  - Honor Roll, 1918-1919 (Box 64, Folder 839)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1899-1905 (Box 64, Folder 840)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1911-1926 (Box 64, Folder 841)
  - Hoo-Hop, 1902-1927 (Box 64, Folder 842-843)
  - Hooker, Richard, 1917-1927 (Box 64, Folder 844)
  - Hoover, Herbert C., 1913-1920 (Box 64, Folder 845)
  - Hope, Walter E., 1912-1924 (Box 64, Folder 846)
  - Hopkins, E. Washburn, 1907-1924 (Box 64, Folder 847)
  - Hor, 1905-1928 (Box 64, Folder 848)
  - Hos-Hov, 1904-1915 (Box 64, Folder 849)
  - Hos-Hov, 1917-1929 (Box 64, Folder 850)
  - Hospitals, 1913-1919 (Box 65, Folder 851)
  - Hotchkiss, H. Stuart, 1907-1920 (Box 65, Folder 852)
  - Houghteling, James L., 1904-1905 (Box 65, Folder 853)
  - How-Hoy, 1902-1929 (Box 65, Folder 854-855)
  - Howe, John Kasson, 1907-1916 (Box 65, Folder 856)
  - Howells and Stokes, Architects: with architectural drawings, 1905-1915 (Box 65, Folder 857)
  - Howland, Charles P., 1903-1928 (Box 65, Folder 858)
  - Howland, Henry E., 1901-1910 (Box 65, Folder 859)
  - Howland Memorial Prize, 1914-1929 (Box 65, Folder 860-861)
  - Hoyt, Eldon II, 1911-1918 (Box 65, Folder 862)
  - Hua-Huk, 1904-1929 (Box 66, Folder 863)
  - Hul-Hum, 1904-1929 (Box 66, Folder 864)
  - Hume, Edward H., 1905-1919 (Box 66, Folder 865-866)
  - Humphreys, May, 1913-1920 (Box 66, Folder 867)
  - Hun, 1902-1928 (Box 66, Folder 868-869)
  - Hunnewell, F.W. II, 1913-1919 (Box 66, Folder 870)
  - Huntington, Archer M., 1906-1926 (Box 66, Folder 871)
  - Huntington, Ellsworth, 1913-1921 (Box 66, Folder 872)
  - Hur, 1903-1924 (Box 66, Folder 873)
  - Hurlbut, William H., 1905-1925 (Box 66, Folder 874)
  - Hus-Huy, 1908-1929 (Box 66, Folder 875)
  - Husted, Mary C., 1910-1911 (Box 66, Folder 876)
  - Hutchings, George S., 1901-1914 (Box 66, Folder 877)
  - Hutchins, Robert M., 1923-1929 (Box 66, Folder 878)
  - Hy, 1905-1928 (Box 66, Folder 879)
  - I-Im, 1909-1923 (Box 67, Folder 880)
  - Ide, George E., 1906-1916 (Box 67, Folder 881)
  - Imbrie, Andrew C., 1912 (Box 67, Folder 882)
  - Immigration, 1924-1929 (Box 67, Folder 883-887)
  - In, 1901-1928 (Box 67, Folder 888-889)
  - Inauguration, James R. Angell, 1921 (Box 67, Folder 890)
  - Industrial Relations, Courses, 1928 (Box 68, Folder 891)
  - Ineson, Stanley B., 1912-1914 (Box 68, Folder 892)
  - Influenza, Dr. Sanford"s reports on, 1918 (Box 68, Folder 893)
  - Ingersoll, J.W.D., 1904-1909 (Box 68, Folder 894)
  - Institute of Human Relations, 1929 (Box 68, Folder 895)
  - Institute of International Education, 1924-1928 (Box 68, Folder 896)
  - Interchurch World Movement, 1919-1920 (Box 68, Folder 897)
  - Intercollegiate Employment Bureau, undated (Box 68, Folder 898)
  - Interdepartmental Charges, 1913 (Box 68, Folder 899)
  - Introduction, Notes of, 1926-1929 (Box 68, Folder 900)
  - Invitations, 1929 (Box 68, Folder 901)
  - Invitations, 1927-1929 (Box 68, Folder 902-905)
  - Invitations, 1927-1929 (Box 69, Folder 906-907)
  - Io-Ir, 1905-1923 (Box 69, Folder 908)
  - Is, 1912-1927 (Box 69, Folder 909)
  - Iv, 1901-1929 (Box 69, Folder 910)
  - Ja, 1901-1929 (Box 69, Folder 911-912)
  - Jaccuci, August F., 1913 (Box 69, Folder 913)
  - Jackson, Percy, 1913-1920 (Box 69, Folder 914)
  - Jacobs, Walter B., 1912-1928 (Box 69, Folder 915)
  - Jaffray, Roger, 1912-1915 (Box 69, Folder 916)
  - Jamestown Exposition, 1906-1907 (Box 69, Folder 917)
  - Jastrow, Morris Jr., 1912-1917 (Box 69, Folder 918)
  - Jay, Pierre, 1901-1924 (Box 69, Folder 919)
  - Je, 1901-1929 (Box 69, Folder 920-921)
  - Jefferson, Rev. Charles, 1905-1920 (Box 70, Folder 922)
  - Jennings, Annie B., 1904-1923 (Box 70, Folder 923)
  - Jennings, Walter, 1905-1921 (Box 70, Folder 924)
  - Jepson, Harry B., 1907-1922 (Box 70, Folder 925)
  - Jewett, Carlton C., 1912-1913 (Box 70, Folder 926)
  - Jo, 1904-1929 (Box 70, Folder 927-930)
  - Johnson, Allen, 1910-1924 (Box 70, Folder 931)
  - Johnson, E.B., 1913-1914 (Box 70, Folder 932)
  - Johnson, Eads, 1910-1912 (Box 70, Folder 933)
  - Johnson, Edward C., 1907-1917 (Box 70, Folder 934)
  - Johnson, Frederick B., 1911-1929 (Box 71, Folder 935-939)
  - Johnson, Mrs. G.A., 1916-1929 (Box 71, Folder 940-941)
  - Johnson, Treat B., 1918-1927 (Box 72, Folder 942)
  - Johnston, George W., 1912-1913 (Box 72, Folder 943)
  - Johnson, John, 1920-1925 (Box 72, Folder 944)
  - Jones, Frederick S., 1910-1929 (Box 72, Folder 945-954)
  - Ju-Jy, 1901-1929 (Box 73, Folder 955-956)
  - Judd, Charles H., 1904-1910 (Box 73, Folder 957-958)
  - Judson, John IV, 1921 (Box 73, Folder 959)
  - Ka, 1905-1927 (Box 73, Folder 960)
  - Ke, 1899-1919 (Box 73, Folder 961-964)
  - Ke, 1920-1929 (Box 74, Folder 965)
  - Keller, Albert G., 1904-1928 (Box 74, Folder 966)
  - Kelsey, Clarence H., 1907-1921 (Box 74, Folder 967)
  - Kendall, William Sergeant, 1913-1915 April (Box 74, Folder 968)
  - Kendall, William Sergeant, 1915 June-1922 (Box 74, Folder 969-972)
  - Keogh, Andrew, 1904-1917 (Box 74, Folder 973-974)
  - Keogh, Andrew, 1918-1919 June (Box 75, Folder 975)
  - Keogh, Andrew, 1919 September-1929 (Box 75, Folder 976-978)
  - Keppel, F.P., 1903-1917 (Box 75, Folder 979)
  - Ki, 1900-1929 (Box 75, Folder 980-981)
  - Kimball, Arthur R., 1907-1919 (Box 75, Folder 982)
  - King, Henry C., 1902-1920 (Box 75, Folder 983)
  - Kingsbury, George O., 1915 (Box 75, Folder 984)
  - Kitchel, C.L., 1900-1924 (Box 75, Folder 985)
  - Kl, 1903-1925 (Box 76, Folder 986)
  - Kn-Ko, 1901-1929 (Box 76, Folder 987-988)
  - Kr-Ky, 1903-1929 (Box 76, Folder 989)
  - La, 1901-1929 (Box 76, Folder 990-994)
  - La Cour, Arthur B., 1912-1915 (Box 77, Folder 995)
  - Lamberton, James M., 1903-1912 (Box 77, Folder 996)
  - Lang, Henry R., 1901-1921 (Box 77, Folder 997)
  - Langzettel, George H., 1903-1923 (Box 77, Folder 998)
  - Law School, 1914-1926 (Box 77, Folder 999)
  - Law School Statistics, 1923 (Box 77, Folder 1000)
  - Lawrie, Lee O., 1908-1919 (Box 77, Folder 1001)
  - Le, 1901-1929 (Box 77, Folder 1002-1007)
  - Leach, Francis A., 1911-1912 (Box 78, Folder 1008)
  - Learned Societies: Annual meeting at Yale University, 1921 December (Box 78, Folder 1009)
  - Lectures, 1919 (Box 78, Folder 1010)
  - Lectures, 1919-1923 (Box 78, Folder 1011-1019)
  - Lectures, 1923-1927 (Box 79, Folder 1020-1030)
  - Lectures, 1927-1929 (Box 80, Folder 1031-1036)
  - Lectures: Bergen, 1922-1929 (Box 80, Folder 1037-1042)
  - Lectures: Bromley, 1922-1929 (Box 80, Folder 1043-1048)
  - Lectures, Dodge: letters re gift of lecture volumes to schools, 1918 (Box 81, Folder 1049)
  - Lectures: Dodge, 1921-1929 (Box 81, Folder 1050-1053)
  - Lectures: Lamont, 1928-1929 (Box 81, Folder 1054)
  - Lectures: Silliman, 1917-1923 (Box 81, Folder 1055)
  - Lectures: Silliman, 1922-1923 (Box 81, Folder 1056)
  - Lectures: Silliman, 1925-1929 (Box 81, Folder 1057-1060)
  - Lectures: Terry, 1924-1925 (Box 81, Folder 1061)
  - Lectures: Terry, 1027-1029 (Box 81, Folder 1062-1063)
  - Lectures: Woodward, 1928-1929 (Box 81, Folder 1064)
  - Leifels, Felix F., 1912 (Box 81, Folder 1065)
  - Lewis, Charlton M., 1901-1923 (Box 81, Folder 1066)
  - Lewis, Dudley P., 1912-1913 (Box 81, Folder 1067)
  - Li-Ll, 1901-1928 (Box 82, Folder 1068-1070)
  - Library, 1905-1924 (Box 82, Folder 1071)
  - Library site, committee on, 1918 (Box 82, Folder 1072)
  - Lima, M. d"Oliverra, 1912 (Box 82, Folder 1073)
  - Linguistics Institute, 1928 (Box 82, Folder 1074)
  - Liquor Law, 1915 (Box 82, Folder 1075)
  - Littig, W.J. & Co., 1907-1915 (Box 82, Folder 1076)
  - Lo-Lol, 1902-1929 (Box 82, Folder 1077)
  - Logie, Elma M., 1916-1920 (Box 82, Folder 1078)
  - Lohmann, Carl A., 1923-1926 (Box 82, Folder 1079)
  - Lom-Lot, 1899-1927 (Box 82, Folder 1080-1081)
  - Lomax, John A., 1914-1917 (Box 82, Folder 1082)
  - Lou-Loy, 1901-1927 (Box 83, Folder 1083-1084)
  - Louvain, 1928-1930 (Box 83, Folder 1085)
  - Lovett, Sidney, undated (Box 83, Folder 1086)
  - Lu, 1899-1929 (Box 83, Folder 1087-1088)
  - Lull, Richard S., 1906-1927 (Box 83, Folder 1089)
  - Louquiens, Frederick B., 1914-1924 (Box 83, Folder 1090)
  - Luther, Willard B., 1913-1923 (Box 83, Folder 1091)
  - Ly, 1905-1928 (Box 83, Folder 1092-1093)
  - McA, 1905-1929 (Box 84, Folder 1094)
  - McB, 1903-1928 (Box 84, Folder 1095)
  - McCa, 1911-1929 (Box 84, Folder 1096)
  - McCl, 1903-1925 (Box 84, Folder 1097-1098)
  - McClelland, J.F., 1909-1916 (Box 84, Folder 1099)
  - McClung, Lee, 1903-1915 (Box 84, Folder 1100-1101)
  - McCo, 1903-1928 (Box 84, Folder 1102)
  - McCormick, Vance, 1903-1928 (Box 84, Folder 1103)
  - McCormick, Vance, 1915-1926 (Box 84, Folder 1104)
  - MacCurdy, George G., 1902-1929 (Box 85, Folder 1105)
  - McCr-McCu, 1903-1928 (Box 85, Folder 1106)
  - McD, 1903-1929 (Box 85, Folder 1107-1108)
  - McE-McG, 1903-1927 (Box 85, Folder 1109-1110)
  - McH-McI, 1903-1923 (Box 85, Folder 1111)
  - McK, 1900-1928 (Box 85, Folder 1112-1113)
  - McL-McZ, 1900-1928 (Box 85, Folder 1114-1116)
  - McL-McZ, 1919-1928 (Box 85, Folder 1116)
  - McLanahan, George X., 1906-1916 (Box 86, Folder 1117)
  - McLane, James W., 1911 (Box 86, Folder 1118)
  - McMullen, F.B., 1913-1915 (Box 86, Folder 1119)
  - Ma-Mai, 1903-1926 (Box 86, Folder 1120-1121)
  - Maintenance, 1919-1921 (Box 86, Folder 1122)
  - Maj- Map, 1900-1928 (Box 86, Folder 1123-1124)
  - Mansfield, Burton, 1912-1913 (Box 86, Folder 1125)
  - Mansfield, Howard, 1901-1920 (Box 86, Folder 1126)
  - Mar, 1900-1928 (Box 86, Folder 1127-1128)
  - Martin, Newell, 1903-1914 (Box 86, Folder 1129)
  - Mas-Maz, 1900-1928 (Box 87, Folder 1130-1132)
  - Mason, George Grant, 1912-1922 (Box 87, Folder 1133-1134)
  - Mathews, Dean C., 1911-1913 (Box 87, Folder 1135)
  - Mathews-Northrup Works, 1917-1918 (Box 87, Folder 1136)
  - Matriculation, 1923-1928 (Box 87, Folder 1137)
  - Mea-Men, 1900-1929 (Box 87, Folder 1138-1139)
  - Medalists, 1926-1927 (Box 87, Folder 1140)
  - Medical School, 1899-1926 (Box 88, Folder 1141-1142)
  - Meeks, Everrett V., 1916-1929 (Box 88, Folder 1143)
  - Memorial Day, 1922-1929 (Box 88, Folder 1144)
  - Memorial plates, 1924-1925 (Box 88, Folder 1145)
  - Memorial Quadrangle, 1920 (Box 88, Folder 1146)
  - Memorials, 1902-1929 (Box 88, Folder 1147)
  - Mendel, Lafayette B., 1902-1929 (Box 88, Folder 1148)
  - Mendell, Clarence W., 1908-1928 (Box 88, Folder 1149)
  - Mendell, Clarence W.: feasibility report re: Summer sessions, 1920 (Box 88, Folder 1150)
  - Mep-Mez, 1901-1919 (Box 88, Folder 1151-1152)
  - Mep-Mez, 1920-1929 (Box 89, Folder 1153)
  - Merrill, Peyson, 1901-1926 (Box 89, Folder 1154)
  - Merritt, Alfred K., 1902-1926 (Box 89, Folder 1155-1157)
  - Messenger Service, 1920 (Box 89, Folder 1158)
  - Messinger, Clifford F., 1911-1917 (Box 89, Folder 1159)
  - Mil, 1905-1928 (Box 89, Folder 1160-1162)
  - Militarized students, minutes of committee on social needs of, 1918 (Box 89, Folder 1163)
  - Military Training Camps, 1926 (Box 89, Folder 1164)
  - Miller, Charles Summer, 1912 (Box 89, Folder 1165)
  - Miller, George Douglas, 1912-1914 (Box 89, Folder 1166)
  - Miller, George Douglas, 1917-1920 (Box 89, Folder 1167)
  - Mim-Miz, 1902-1926 (Box 90, Folder 1168-1170)
  - Mitchell, John R., 1912-1913 (Box 90, Folder 1171)
  - Moa-Mol, 1902-1926 (Box 90, Folder 1172)
  - Mon, 1903-1928 (Box 90, Folder 1173)
  - Moo, 1900-1929 (Box 90, Folder 1174-1175)
  - Mor, 1902-1929 (Box 90, Folder 1176-1179)
  - Morgan, Herbert M., 1914-1915 (Box 91, Folder 1180)
  - Morris, Edward P., [1900-1919] (Box 91, Folder 1181)
  - Morse, William H., 1903-1914 (Box 91, Folder 1182)
  - Mos-Moz, 1903-1929 (Box 91, Folder 1183-1184)
  - Motion Pictures, Report to the Committee on, 1914 (Box 91, Folder 1185)